techperk.com 2011-11-10

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

We consider that the privacy and safety of your personal information as a highly important one. At TechPerk, we do not share your information with anybody and do not use it for any commercial purpose. When we ask for your information then it is solely for purpose of the website. Any extended information asked from you is accompanied by prior notification. Please make sure that you do not submit your personal and crucial information to any external websites that claim to be associated with TechPerk unless notified.

**Disclosure**

The TechPerk is a website created to provide incredible content, which is informational as well.  
It is hereby declared that the content and the posts on the website would not be affected by the amount paid. The advertisements placement on the sites is done by third party agencies and would be regarded as Paid Advertising.

There are instances when TechPerk gets payments from publishing its’ posts on various places for reviews on services, websites, products or myriad topics. The TechPerk receives compensation as a medium and the opinions, discussions and comments do not belong to the website. They are purely related to the bloggers. Thus, the sources and notTech Perk must verify the statistics, representations etc.

TechPerk has a connection with a variety of sites to get links for products, which are related to Third party Agencies. At TechPerk we affirm that no information will be published that may result in any kind of conflicts whatsoever intentionally.

**Financial Information**

At TechPerk, we do not demand your credit card details or ask you to enter your password anywhere. So kindly do not offer such information anywhere, especially in emails.

**Cookies Policy**

When you submit any information on the website then a small data file called “Cookie” helps us in recognizing you when you visit TechPerk again. With the help of cookie, we save your customization information. However, these files do not capture any personal information. There may be few cookies in Techperk used by third party providers as well.

**Google and DART Cookies**

There are advertisements published on the site, which are proposed by Google. They make use of the DART Cookies that enables to present ads to the users pertaining to the record of their internet surfing details. In case you wish to disable the tracking then you can visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
**  
User Information Usage**

TechPerk makes use of Google Analytics for tracking purposes and statistical analysis. Therefore some of your details like Address, Browser and OS etc may be recorded by our website. However, we assure that the information is made use only for stats and not shared with anybody else.

**The Associated Risks of Accessing Internet**

There are many efforts, which we put in to safeguard your information however this cannot be guaranteed as the transition of information in the internet is wide. You must keep a check on your passwords and username security. A lot of third party sites and services can be linked to TechPerk, which is independent of our policies. Thus, we cannot take any responsibility what-so-ever of the safety measures on other sites.

**Comments Made by Users are Not TechPerk Derivatives**

At the Tech Perk, the visitors are allowed to present their views and comments. Even though content is present on the site, we do not hold responsibility of the ideas and content as comments. Moreover, the site administration has complete authority to remove any unsuitable content, which it feels inappropriate. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

TechPerk has the full rights to change the above Privacy Policy at its own discretion.  
If you have any queries regarding the Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us through the Contact Us Page.
